{
  "inner": [
    {
      "front": "to love (romantically)",
      "back": "ài",
      "accuracy": [
        100.0,
        90.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "to be (not adjectives)",
      "back": "shì",
      "accuracy": [
        100.0,
        87.5
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "i",
      "back": "wǒ",
      "accuracy": [
        100.0,
        100.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "hello",
      "back": "nǐhǎo",
      "accuracy": [
        100.0,
        90.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "it",
      "back": "tā",
      "accuracy": [
        100.0,
        100.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "to be (adjective)",
      "back": "hěn",
      "accuracy": [
        100.0,
        90.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "you",
      "back": "nǐ",
      "accuracy": [
        100.0,
        90.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "not",
      "back": "bù",
      "accuracy": [
        100.0,
        87.5
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "and",
      "back": "hé",
      "accuracy": [
        100.0,
        87.5
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "posession particle (pronoun + posession particle = possessive pronoun)",
      "back": "de",
      "accuracy": [
        100.0,
        87.5
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "plural marker for people",
      "back": "men",
      "accuracy": [
        87.5,
        65.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "good",
      "back": "hǎo",
      "accuracy": [
        87.5,
        65.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "dad",
      "back": "bàba",
      "accuracy": [
        50.0,
        40.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "very/quite",
      "back": "hěn",
      "accuracy": [
        50.0,
        40.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "mum/mummy",
      "back": "māma",
      "accuracy": [
        50.0,
        40.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "to feel (physical and emotional)",
      "back": "gǎnjué",
      "accuracy": [
        40.0,
        50.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "just (happened)",
      "back": "gāng",
      "accuracy": [
        40.0,
        55.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "to have/possess",
      "back": "yǒu",
      "accuracy": [
        40.0,
        50.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "thank you",
      "back": "xièxie",
      "accuracy": [
        40.0,
        50.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "but/however/yet (formal)",
      "back": "dànshì",
      "accuracy": [
        40.0,
        50.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "to think",
      "back": "xiǎng",
      "accuracy": [
        25.0,
        40.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "but/however (informal)",
      "back": "kěshì",
      "accuracy": [
        25.0,
        40.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "to do/make",
      "back": "zuò",
      "accuracy": [
        25.0,
        40.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "to see/watch/look at",
      "back": "kàn",
      "accuracy": [
        25.0,
        40.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "to go",
      "back": "qù",
      "accuracy": [
        25.0,
        40.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "now",
      "back": "xiànzài",
      "accuracy": [
        25.0,
        40.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "if (to form hypotheticals such as \"if...then...\", not to express uncertainty such as \"she doesn't know if...\")",
      "back": "rúguǒ",
      "accuracy": [
        2.5,
        25.0
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "to need",
      "back": "xūyào",
      "accuracy": [
        2.5,
        25.0
      ]
    }
  ]
}
}